It's more fun if two people lick together
2人で一緒に舐めた方が楽しい
is.
です
Both of you are amazing.
2人 ともすごいね
It was my first experience.
初体験しちゃったね
Come to this bed for a moment, both of you.
ちょっとこのベッドおいでよ、2人とも
Two people,
2人がさ、
It's not bad.
や ばくないね
Aren't you both dangerous?
2人ともやばくない?
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
Which one will you do?
どっちかやる?
Which one should I do?
ど っち かやる?
Which one will you do?
どっちかやる?
I'll decide.
決めるから
Come here, both of you.
2人ともこっちおいでよ
Just once, stick your butt out.
一回さ、尻つき出してさ
I'll play pussy roulette.
おまんこルーレットやるから
Look at the camera.
カメラ見てね
Which should I choose?
どっちにしようかな?
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
It's your first time seeing it, right?
初めて見たでしょ?
Chu
チュ
- Let's do it, the two of us.
ー してこら、2人で
want?
欲しい?
I did it here.
こっちにしちゃった
My pussy has a different body shape.
おまん、ちがううでさに
Why not me?
なんで私じゃないの?
You look like that though.
みたいな顔してるけど
I'll do it later.
後でしてあげるから
Two people,
2人で、
Kanashi is the best.
な かなし最高って
Nakanashi is the best
なかなし最高